This is a man's jacket.
Enter the picture window and double-click on the file named avatar.
Enter mirv2 and double-click on the file mv2henry.mvt or drag it into the 3D window.
Open the printfiles folder in the picture window.
This is the B-Basic B-Jumper folder that was installed in the cloud in order to do the cloud tutorial.
Double-click on the file jumper-mirv.dxf or drag it into the 2D or 3D window.
Use the adjustment sheet tool in the 2D window.
Arrange the sheets together so that it will be easier to arrange later.
In the 2D tool channel, use the编辑版片工具 and right-click on the middle bar.
Come out of the menu and choose simple chain .
In the 2D tool channel, select the adjustment sheets tool.
Select the sheets to remove the middle and steam out of the frame.
In the menu, select the column-linked version, the symmetrical version, the version and the
3D window, select the 3D vertical tool bar 4, click on the display point, the second icon in the level display virtual model series, and the blue point will be displayed around the 3D window virtual model.
In the 2D window, select all the panels or press Ctrl A to select all the panels, move the panels up and remove the blocked points.
In the 2D window, select all the panels in the front or press Ctrl A to select all the panels.
Then press Ctrl A and
ured shift to the front panel.
Move the mouse to the 3D window.
On the 3D location, one left click will assign panels to the model, around the model.
Race to the rear view of view by clicking on a shortcut , then move the mouse to the 3D location on the left click to assign panels around the model.
Select the collar plate, arrange the plate on the center point of the back neck.
Select the sleeve plate, select the arrangement point above the arm,
stop the mouse to the fourth of the 3D vertical tool bar,
press the display arrangement point, hide the arrangement point.
Select the line sewing tool in the 2D window,
sew the front and back, pay attention to the direction before sewing when sewing.
Use the line sewing tool to sew the sleeves, pay attention to the direction before sewing.
Use the line sewing tool to sew the sleeves to the sleeve.
Pay attention to the direction before sewing.
Use the line sewing tool to sew the collar to the collar.
Select the collar plate, press the shift key,
select the collar line according to the direction before sewing,
after sewing, release the shift key.
Sew the bottom, pay attention to the direction before sewing.
Rotate the 3D window,
check if the seam line is correct.
Check if the seam line is correct.
Select the 3D tool bar,
select the 3D clothing,
press the left button on the top of the collar plate,
slide the mouse to the bottom of the clothing plate,
press the left button.
Repeat operation on the other side.
The 3D zipper will automatically find the add-on object according to the seam line relationship.
Create the 3D tool bar,
select the tool.
Press the simulation button,
the pattern will naturally be bound to the model.
Close the simulation and close the simulation.
Enter the taskbar window,
and insert the double click to enter the mealv2 file address.
Open the PoS file address,
Double-click on the mv203 file or drag it into the 3D window.
Click OK.
Change the model's position to a vertical position.
Enter the drawing window.
Enter the FABRIK file.
Drag the material into the object window FABRIK1.
Loosen the mouse.
Open the simulation.
Apply the material to 3D clothing.
Close the simulation after the simulation is complete.
Choose the move tool in the 3D window.
Press the left button on the 3D pull head.
Move along the center line of the pull chain.
You can see a gray shadow on the ruler.
Loosen the mouse.
Open the simulation.
The upper part of the pull chain will be opened.
Close the simulation.
Press the left button on the pull chain.
Move along the ruler to the top.
Loosen the mouse.
Open the simulation again.
The pull chain will be rewound.
Loosen the pull chain at the edge.
Choose the move tool.
Pull the model to the bottom.
Move along the ruler.
Open the triangle.
Choose the trim hardware.
Open the simulation.
Apply the settings to the 3D clothing.
Loosen the pull chain.
Close the simulation after the simulation is complete.
Close the simulation.
Choose the polyester tuft in the object window.
Click copy.
Copy the polyester tuft.
The polyester tuft copied is the same as the polyester tuft.
Choose the color you need in the 2D window or 3D window.
Press Shift to select.
In the object window,
click on the application button next to Copy On.
Apply Copy On to the panel.
Change the color in the property editor.
Press Shift to edit.
In the object window,
choose the polyester tuft.
In the property editor,
adjust the color.
Press Shift to edit.
In the 3D window,
choose the pull chain.
You can change the color of the puller in the attribute type.
You can modify the appearance of the puller in the attribute type.
Select plastic to give the puller a plastic reflection type.
Select the puller in the 3D window.
You can modify the shape of the puller and puller in the attribute editor type.
Select plastic to give the puller a plastic reflection type.
You can modify the shape of the puller in the attribute type.
You can modify the shape of the puller.
In the 3D window, select the tool to improve the clothing quality, click on the menu to confirm.
Open the simulation and set it to 3D clothing.
After the simulation is completed, turn off the simulation.
Select the Nature
Now you can change the color of the clothing.
Click on the master, and see the display.
You can also add or change the color of your clothing.
Click the master button.
Here you can change the color of clothes. You can also add or change the color of clothing. You can also add or change the color of clothing.